[
  {
    "answer": "You console it.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/06/2013",
    "question": "How do you comfort a JavaScript bug?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "q. How do you comfort a JavaScript bug? a. You console it."
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because its parent kept giving it `props`!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "05/22/2017",
    "question": "Why did the child component have such great self-esteem?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the child component have such great self-esteem? a. Because its parent kept giving it `props`!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because they use a strongly typed language",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/23/2013",
    "question": "Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "java",
      "c#"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why do C# and Java developers keep breaking their keyboards? a. Because they use a strongly typed language!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "05/22/2017",
    "question": "Why did the functional component feel lost?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the functional component feel lost? a. Because it didn't know what `state` it was in!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/10/2013",
    "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "node"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why was the JavaScript developer sad? a. Because he didn't Node how to Express himself!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because he used up all his cache!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/17/2013",
    "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
    "tags": [],
    "text": "q. Why did the developer go broke? a. Because he used up all his cache!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "10/31/2017",
    "question": "Why did the React Higher Order Component give up?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the React Higher Order Component give up? a. Because it sur-rendered to the prop-aganda!"
  },
  {
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/09/2013",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "When a JavaScript date has gone bad, \"Don't call me, I'll callback you. I promise!\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because it was now off the hook.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "question": "Why did the react class component feel relieved?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the react class component feel relieved? a. Because it was now off the hook."
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because they were completely hooked on the hooks proposal.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "question": "Why did the react developer have an addiction?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the react developer have an addiction? a. Because they were completely hooked on the hooks proposal."
  },
  {
    "answer": "It means to swallow something hook, line and sinker.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "question": "What does a React proposal mean?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. What does a React proposal mean? a. It means to swallow something hook, line and sinker."
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because they were playing hooky with the hooks proposal.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "question": "Why was the react developer late to everything?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why was the react developer late to everything? a. Because they were playing hooky with the hooks proposal"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because it didn\u2019t get the context.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "11/27/2018",
    "question": "Why couldn\u2019t the React component understand the joke?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "react"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why couldn\u2019t the React component understand the joke? a. Because it didn\u2019t get the context."
  },
  {
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/09/2013",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "Dev1 saw a strange JavaScript function & asked, \"What is this?\". Dev2 responded, \"I don't know. I would've called you, but I was in a bind\""
  },
  {
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/10/2013",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "Two JavaScript developers walked into the variable `bar`. Ouch!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/11/2013",
    "question": "Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did Jason cover himself with bubble wrap? a. Because he wanted to make a cross-domain JSONP request."
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because they needed JavaScript experts!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/12/2013",
    "question": "Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the software company hire drama majors from Starbucks? a. Because they needed JavaScript experts!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because he couldn't find his source without a map!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/13/2013",
    "question": "Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "coffeescript"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the CoffeeScript developer keep getting lost? a. Because he couldn't find his source without a map!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "__mifflin__",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/16/2013",
    "question": "What do you call __proto__? Dunder proto. Michael Scott was the regional manager where?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript"
    ],
    "text": "q. What do you call __proto__? a. Dunder proto q. Michael Scott was the regional manager where? a. __mifflin__"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/16/2013",
    "question": "How did the doctor revive the developer?",
    "tags": [
      "css"
    ],
    "text": "q. How did the doctor revive the developer? a. The dev wasn't responsive so the doc picked him up by his bootstraps!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because he didn't like Java.",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/18/2013",
    "question": "Why did the C# developer fall asleep?",
    "tags": [
      "java",
      "c#"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the C# developer fall asleep? a. Because he didn't like Java."
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/19/2013",
    "question": "Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "knockout",
      "backbone"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why did the JavaScript boxer goto the chiropractor? a. Because his backbone was angular from a knockout and required attention!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\"",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/20/2013",
    "question": "How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings?",
    "tags": [
      "css"
    ],
    "text": "q. How did the web dev hurt Comic Sans feelings? a. Once he saw the font he quickly changed to Open Sans and exclaimed \"In your @font-face!\""
  },
  {
    "answer": "Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!",
    "author": "elijahmanor",
    "created": "09/24/2013",
    "question": "Why was Ember.js turning red?",
    "tags": [
      "javascript",
      "ember"
    ],
    "text": "q. Why was Ember.js turning red? a. Because it was EMBERrassed for not remEMBERing its route home!"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It'll be a real pain in their ASP!",
    "author": "BMDan",
    "created": "2019-05-01",
    "question": "Why is Microsoft afraid of Python as a Web language?",
    "tags": [
      "python",
      "asp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "No double-inheritance.",
    "author": "BMDan",
    "created": "2019-05-01",
    "question": "Why did Java stop having children after the first arrived?",
    "tags": [
      "java"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "Functools partials, a few lambdas, most def.",
    "author": "BMDan",
    "created": "2019-05-01",
    "question": "How do the cool kids write their programs' functions nowadays?",
    "tags": [
      "python"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "__mifflin__",
    "author": "BMDan (based on elijahmanor)",
    "created": "2019-05-01",
    "question": "Where was Michael Scott the regional manager?",
    "tags": [
      "python"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "from __future__ import...",
    "author": "BMDan",
    "created": "2019-05-01",
    "question": "Is there any way to see the hot new movie if it hasn't been released in your country yet?",
    "tags": [
      "python"
    ]
  }
]
